When you raise Hell...the Devil must be paid - in full!
Rock 'n' Roll Nightmare is a horror, music film directed by John Fasano.
At an old farmhouse, a family mysteriously dissapears at the hands of evil.
Years later, hair metal band The Tritons comes to the farmhouse,
whose barn now features a 24-track recording studio.
Lead singer John Triton gets the band to perform their first night in the farmhouse after dinner,
and weird little beasties suddenly appear, and strange things start to happen.
Band members (and their tagalong girlfriends) begin to
act strangely and vanish one by one.
Soon, only John Triton remains, and he holds a secret.
Finally, the evil shows itself and a battle between heaven and hell ensues....
John Triton, played by Jon Mikl Thor.
Lou Anne, played by Jillian Peri.
Roger Eburt, played by Frank Dietz.
Randy, played by Teresa Simpson.
Phil, played by Adam Fried.
Dee Dee, played by Denise Dicandia.
Rock 'n' Roll Nightmare (also known as The Edge of Hell) is a 1987 Canadian direct-to-video horror film directed
by John Fasano, and stars heavy metal musician Jon Mikl Thor, Jillian Peri and Teresa Simpson.
The film explores themes of supernatural, heavy metal, satan.
The tone is dark.